Get out.
You don't have to order me around.
You didn't even realize
you'd been kidnapped?
You're quite the dummy.
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
Six!
Seven!
Eight!
Nine!
I was raised to be the Annovazzi
family heir despite being the youngest
because I was the strongest
of all my sisters.
Ten!
You handled yourself quite impressively.
You saw everything! It's over!
My life as a noblewoman is over!
That must've been quite the fright.
You poor thing.
No one's ever said that to me before.
Mimi.
Marry me.
What?
Always a Catch!
Knight Captain
Episode 3
How I Trained to Become a Lady
You look beautiful.
Really?
Yes. You look like a lovely
lady from every angle.
Even the king and queen
will sing your praises.
What should I do? I'm so nervous.
WANDER WANDER
Things progressed rapidly after that.
Baron Casciari and Lady Eleonora were
arrested for bribery and kidnapping.
The crown prince ceremony
was held afterwards,
with Renato becoming crown prince.
About your meeting with my family...
Your family...
You mean royals!
This is the date and time.
You've already scheduled it?!
Today is the day
I formally become engaged.
I wonder what Prince Renato's
family are like.
I hope they're as friendly
as Prince Placido.
Lady Maria!
ZOOM
Act like a lady. Don't do anything weird.
It's okay.
I practiced a bunch with Aida, so... uh...
Where am I?
Lady Maria!
I'm terribly sorry!
She's so quick. By the time
we noticed, she was gone.
Well, that's Mimi. It can't be helped.
She can't have left the castle grounds.
Search every corner.
Yes, sir!
I feel like I passed through here earlier.
We found her, Your Highness.
This way.
Mimi?
Prince Renato.
Are you all right? Are you hurt?
Oh, I'm totally fine.
What happened?
Um, I found him.
He was lost in the bushes.
My little Macaron!
Where have you been?
I've been looking for you.
What? He's Your Majesty's puppy?
Yes. I've been so worried.
Thank you for finding him,
Ms. Maria Annovazzi.
Not at all.
Not only did I keep you waiting,
but I'm a mess.
What an amusing young lady.
Father!
It's rude to laugh so much.
AH HA HA HA
Um, Your Highness, I...
That's my Mimi.
I've never seen Renato
make that expression before.
It's not easy to find a girl like her.
Where in the world did he find her?
Right, darling?
HMPH
In any case, I became
crown princess on this day.
I'd better study hard so I can
become a lovely crown princess.
Good grief.
Ladies don't skip through
the royal academy halls.
Mimi.
STOP!
You mustn't skip.
You're making everyone else
get out of your way.
Sorry, Aida.
Let's work hard to make you
a crown princess, okay?
Okay. I look forward to
learning with you.
But originally, you were supposed to
become the crown princess.
If this damages your reputation...
You don't need to worry about that, Mimi.
I feel like Aida's been
more cheerful recently.
Very well, Aida. Thank you.
But ideally, I'd like to start
training after our next break.
I'm going back home.
I finally get to see my baby
brother Teodorico again.
Oh, you settled on dates?
I thought you wouldn't
be going until later.
You have so much to prepare.
Prince Placido said Prince Renato
wouldn't want to let you go.
Aw, really?
Oh, right.
That's why I'm going to the royal
castle to see His Highness today.
Very well.
Then I'll head home without you.
Thanks.
I'll be home in time for dinner.
LOOM...
And now she's running.
You're here, Lord Raimondo?
Will her training go all right?
You've seen how it's going.
But she's athletic. She'll pick up
on royal etiquette quickly.
Can anything be done about
her habit of speaking her mind?
Actually, I'm leaving that the way it is.
It's one of her strengths.
But that could lead
to trouble once she becomes queen.
It's all right.
She doesn't think thoughts
that would upset others.
Probably not, anyway.
Watch this. Speak of the devil.
That's Lady Rosalia Pinotti,
the marquis' daughter
who'd been pursuing Prince Renato.
I heard she harassed you quite a bit.
Why, Lady Maria, how do you do?
HUH?
How do you do, Lady Rosalia?
No wonder this area
smells like the countryside.
Indeed, Lady Rosalia.
Do I smell a pasture?
You betray your origins.
I hope your stench doesn't make
Prince Renato fall out of love with you.
You smell lovely, Lady Rosalia.
Are you wearing perfume?
Of course. All ladies wear perfume.
Are you unaware the Pinotti Marquisate
is famous for its perfume?
Perhaps you've never seen perfume
made using natural essential oils.
Natural essential oil perfume?
Do you have that with you now?
TWITCH
I shall let you in on a little secret.
Our perfumes aren't just fragrant.
They're moisturizing as well.
They also contain ground shells,
which make your skin more beautiful.
See?
RUB RUB
It smells lovely.
It really does make your skin sparkle.
Doesn't it?
Perfume amazing. Want to take home.
Why are you speaking like that?
They speak common in the Kingdom of Muro.
What? Lady Rosalia, you're familiar
with the Kingdom of Muro?
Of course. As a noble,
I've studied all the nearby nations.
Thank you!
SWING
I'm delighted you even
studied my little kingdom!
It's a shame you had to
grow up in the countryside
surrounded by nothing but pastures.
I doubt you've ever been to the beach.
You're right.
Have you been, Lady Rosalia?
I enjoy vacationing by the sea
every year at my villa.
Wow, that sounds lovely.
I'd love to see the blue seas
and glittering spray.
The seafood must be delicious as well.
And at night, you can enjoy fireworks.
The stars must be beautiful, too.
I'd love to visit.
Lady Rosalia, don't be fooled
into thinking that might be fun!
Lady Rosalia, come to your senses!
I don't have a swimsuit.
Would you help me choose one?
QUIVER
Lady Rosalia!
What's wrong with you?
I'll invite you to vacation with me
this summer, so prepare yourself!
I'll contact my childhood friend's store
regarding a swimsuit for you!
You'd better be prepared...
for what's in store!
Lady Rosalia!
Okay! I'm looking forward to it!
See?
What am I supposed to be seeing?
Mimi even treats Lady Rosalia that way.
And she'd fight everyone off
if they bothered her physically.
It's good that she's so tough.
Didn't her meeting the other day go well?
Yes, mostly.
Mostly?
There's something
I must give to Lady Maria.
I'll see you later.
STEP STEP STEP STEP...
Later!
Hey, Lord Raimondo.
Good timing.
Lady Maria?
Look.
This kitty is lost.
This reminds me of your
meeting and the queen.
She doesn't like me, does she?
Aida said the queen seemed interested
when she told her about me before.
I definitely disappointed her.
The queen is rather
strict about etiquette.
The king and queen dowager like you,
but the queen has doubts that you're
worthy of being crown princess of Rubini.
I'd like to be on friendly terms.
After all, she's Prince Renato's mother.
There's no point
in worrying about the past.
What's this?
An invitation from the queen.
She'd like the two of you to have tea.
This may be a test.
Always a Catch!
Mimi, I'm sorry for keeping you waiting.
Your Highness, did you run here?
Forgive me. I was in a hurry.
Oh, no. I'm fine.
SO HANDSOME
You seem quite busy.
Yes. I suddenly have so much more to do.
That's why I couldn't wait to see you.
BLUSH
That hairpin suits you.
What? Oh, this?
It's worn by direct female descendants
of the Annovazzi family.
They're based on our family crest,
but each design is custom made.
When we marry, our partner's family crest
is incorporated into the design.
Then you'll have to get a new one
made based on the royal crest.
The royal crest?
B-But I'm not worthy.
Don't say that.
It's your family tradition, is it not?
Your Highness...
Thank you.
My family will be delighted as well.
I must tell them when I return.
About that...
GLOOM...
Do you promise you'll come back?
Of course.
SMILE
I have school.
GLOOM...
A-And I want to see you again.
SMILE
Good.
He doesn't need to worry so much.
But this lovely prince makes time
for me and notices my hairpin.
It's disconcerting, but
it makes me so happy, too.
But I might not want to leave
once I see Teodorico.
Just kidding.
That's your baby brother, isn't it?
I spoke my mind again!
I'm already used to that habit of yours.
Likewise.
I brought you the list, Your Highness.
Thank you.
This is a list of gifts
for the Annovazzi family.
I hope they like them.
THUMP
We love receiving anything
that doesn't make us sick.
That's encouraging.
Also, is one day enough
to see your family?
What? That's so short.
I told him that was too short, too.
It takes six days
to travel there and back.
We can take our time when
I go with you to see your family.
Your Highness, Lord Raimondo is watching.
I don't mind.
STRUGGLE
You're surprisingly strong, aren't you?
Am I?
Actually, your movements are
so dull, it's harder to escape.
What is this? You're scaring me.
SURRENDER
I can't wait to give you a new hairpin.
KISS
OVER CAPACITY
Um, Prince Renato...
Your Highness, Lady Maria is having
tea with the queen after this.
Please release her.
Mother scheduled her tea party
to interrupt our time together.
That's not nice of her.
It can't be helped.
It seems the queen doesn't like me much.
I don't think that's true.
I'll see you again
before I leave for Muro.
Don't work too hard.
See you later.
Prince Renato assigned knights to me
even within the castle.
Not to guard me, but to
prevent me from getting lost.
I want to be protected, too.
I thought I sensed someone.
So this is the queen's garden.
Lady Maria, we've been waiting for you.
Where is the queen?
She'll be here shortly. Please wait here.
How do you do?
Th-Thank you for inviting me today.
I hope you are well, Your Majesty.
No need to be so formal.
Have a seat.
Y-Yes, ma'am.
STARE...
She's staring so much!
Did I screw up my initial greeting?
She sighed!
What should I do?
It's been five seconds, and
she's already sick of me!
Uh, um... etiquette... tea... treats...
YOINK
Start with the tastiest treats.
Thank you.
That's right. Calm down.
When acting like a lady, take small bites.
Drink your tea without making a sound.
And smile gently.
It's delicious.
How's that?
BANG
"How's that?"
Were you speaking to me?
I spoke my mind again! I'm sorry!
Well, your manners are acceptable.
Th-Thank you.
Your Majesty, watch out!
Your Majesty!
That came from a castle window.
Who did this?
Lady Maria, are you hurt?
I'm fine.
More importantly, the queen and culprit...
She's shaking. Of course she is.
She was suddenly attacked.
That must've been terrifying.
Your Majesty, you're all right now.
Let's return to your room.
Can you stand?
SHOVE
I can't.
What?
I can't take it anymore!
You are so super cool, Mimi! I adore you!
What?
You're as strong as Aida said you were!
Did you see how she kicked
the table into the air?
I wish I could've seen you fight
Baron Casciari's assassins!
Why does Renato get everything?
It's not fair!
Y-Your Majesty, you
mustn't slap the ground.
SLAP
You're simply the best, Mimi!
You're so cool!
SLAP
You'll get your hands dirty.
I don't care!
SLAP
I'll dirty my hands if that's
what it takes to praise your valor!
SLAP
I love you, Mimi! Squee!
I'm not sure what happened,
but she's lost her mind.
I love, love, love you!
Take her to a doctor quickly.
Yes, ma'am.
DRAG DRAG
Stay here tonight, Mimi!
Mimi!
What was that about?
Well, well. You're even more
interesting than expected, Mimi.
To be continued
Translation:
Timing:
Sho Stifler
Mariana Martinez
Editing:
Quality Control:
Alicia Ashby
Ashley Barboza
Final Quality Control:     Michelle Tymon
The queen showed me that tiara.
It had so many big jewels.
I was surprised by how heavy it was.
The queen is quite the tough woman.
Next Time
How the One That Got Away Was Troubled
After all, she and the king actually...
Oh, I spoke my mind again!